<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<changelogs>
    <changelog>
        <element>mod_jt_image_accordion</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>0.3.4</version>
        <note>
            <item>JED Checker compliance update focused on Joomla Manual license header alignment.</item>
        </note>
        <addition>
            <item>Added LICENSE.txt to the installation package.</item>
        </addition>
        <change>
            <item>Updated module version to 0.3.4.</item>
            <item>Updated PHP file headers to match the Joomla Manual license format.</item>
            <item>Changed PHP file license headers to GNU General Public License version 2 or later; see LICENSE.txt.</item>
            <item>Updated manifest file list to include LICENSE.txt.</item>
            <item>Updated media asset registry version to 0.3.4.</item>
        </change>
        <fix>
            <item>Improved JED Checker compatibility by aligning license metadata with Joomla extension examples.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>mod_jt_image_accordion</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>0.3.3</version>
        <note>
            <item>Manifest license compatibility update for Joomla Manual alignment.</item>
        </note>
        <change>
            <item>Updated module version to 0.3.3.</item>
            <item>Updated the manifest license value to GNU General Public License version 2 or later.</item>
            <item>Updated media asset registry version to 0.3.3.</item>
        </change>
        <fix>
            <item>Improved JED Checker compatibility for manifest license validation.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>mod_jt_image_accordion</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>0.3.2</version>
        <note>
            <item>Manifest validation update for JED Checker compatibility.</item>
        </note>
        <change>
            <item>Updated module version to 0.3.2.</item>
            <item>Updated media asset registry version to 0.3.2.</item>
        </change>
        <fix>
            <item>Removed the unsupported php_minimum element from the extension manifest.</item>
            <item>Kept PHP minimum requirement handling in the Joomla update server XML only.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>mod_jt_image_accordion</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>0.3.1</version>
        <note>
            <item>Patch release focused on Bootstrap 5 button output and Joomla administrator naming.</item>
        </note>
        <change>
            <item>Updated module version to 0.3.1.</item>
            <item>Updated the Joomla administrator module name to JT Image Accordion.</item>
            <item>Updated administrator language strings for consistent extension naming.</item>
        </change>
        <fix>
            <item>Removed legacy jt-accordion-card__button class from frontend button markup.</item>
            <item>Normalized saved legacy jt-btn-hover-* button values to native Bootstrap 5 btn-* classes.</item>
            <item>Prevented custom accordion button classes from appearing in frontend output.</item>
            <item>Fixed inconsistent module naming in Joomla administrator module listings.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>mod_jt_image_accordion</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>0.3.0</version>
        <note>
            <item>Maintenance and compatibility release focused on Joomla 6.1.x and Bootstrap 5 alignment.</item>
        </note>
        <addition>
            <item>Added a new parameter to optionally display sample cards.</item>
            <item>Added Bootstrap modal dependency to the Web Asset Manager asset definition.</item>
        </addition>
        <change>
            <item>Updated module version to 0.3.0.</item>
            <item>Changed frontend button rendering to use native Bootstrap 5 btn-* classes directly.</item>
            <item>Removed custom jt-btn-hover-* button style handling.</item>
            <item>Cleaned up custom CSS to avoid duplicating Bootstrap 5 button behavior.</item>
            <item>Simplified modal markup by relying more on Bootstrap 5 utility classes.</item>
            <item>Disabled automatic sample card rendering by default for safer production usage.</item>
            <item>Updated media asset registry version to 0.3.0.</item>
            <item>Updated English and Turkish administrator language strings.</item>
        </change>
        <fix>
            <item>Prevented sample content from appearing unintentionally on the frontend when no cards are configured.</item>
            <item>Blocked data: image URI usage in image fields.</item>
            <item>Filtered unsafe CTA URL schemes such as javascript: and vbscript:.</item>
            <item>Prevented negative CSS size values from being accepted.</item>
            <item>Removed unnecessary fallback modal styling and scripting complexity.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>mod_jt_image_accordion</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>0.2.0</version>
        <note>
            <item>First JoomTheme-branded test release under the mod_jt_image_accordion element.</item>
        </note>
        <addition>
            <item>Added hover image accordion layout with Bootstrap 5 modal support.</item>
            <item>Added optional diagonal modal opening animation.</item>
            <item>Added repeatable card fields for image, description, button and modal content.</item>
            <item>Added Joomla update server and changelog XML support.</item>
        </addition>
        <change>
            <item>Updated display name to JoomTheme Image Accordion.</item>
            <item>Improved Turkish and English administrator language strings.</item>
            <item>Updated asset registry names and media destination to mod_jt_image_accordion.</item>
        </change>
        <fix>
            <item>Normalized module element, language prefix and PHP namespace for the new repository name.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>
</changelogs>
